Bobby Moynihan

Font-End Developer

- b.3.moynihan@gmail.com
- github.com/itBme3
- github.com/itBme3

Skills:

Javascript

Typescript

CSS

SCSS

HTML

Nuxt

Vue

Svelte

Angular

Jquery

Tailwind

Graphic design

Education:

The School of the Art Institute in Chicago (Graphic Design)

Summary:

Self taught programmer - trained designer.

Addicted to learning — especially new/better ways of doing things I already thought I knew.

Art school taught me how to take criticism (leaving emotion out of it) and building off of feedback.

Entrepreneurship taught to be self-reliant at solving problems and implementing solutions.

My most consistent and valued skill during 10+ years in web development has been proficient google searching. There have been few (if any) problems I have not been able to find/build solutions for — while staying on-budget.

Work Experience:

Frontend Consultant

Get it Got (2018-2022)

Worked intimately with small/mid-sized companies to create web-based solutions that increased bottom line. Our most consistent client saw 10x lift in online revenue after working with us — and maintains a conversion rate that is 3x better than industry average (which was what their original conversion rate was).

What I did:

- Frontend web development for ecommerce & marketing sites
- Developed apps (used internally) to better connect various 3rd-party APIs & improve productivity
- UI/UX design
- Collaboration with clients and their teams to develop solutions for improving & automating web-based marketing

Bobby Moynihan

Font-End Developer

- b.3.moynihan@gmail.com
- github.com/itBme3
- github.com/itBme3

Skills:

Javascript

Typescript

CSS

SCSS

HTML

Nuxt

Vue

Svelte

Angular

Jquery

Tailwind

Graphic design

Education:

The School of the Art Institute in Chicago (Graphic Design)

Work Experience Continued:

Brand/Frontend Consultant

Get it Got (2016-2018)

Worked with clients to develop & implement SOW.

As co-founder, I was also responsible for creating core business processes.

What I did:

- Worked with executives to establish their company's brand identity.
- Developed apps (used internally) to better connect various 3rd-party APIs & improve productivity
- UI/UX design
- Collaboration with clients and their teams to develop solutions for improving & automating web-based marketing

Chief Creative Officer

Tiesta Tea (2009-2016)

As employee #1, I wore many hats — from developing visual identity, to creating our ecommerce store.

The brand & design systems I developed, continue to be used and expanded upon today. Tiesta Tea is now an 8 figure company.

What I did:

- Create/maintain brand & visual identity
- Create ecommerce store
- Developed online presence
- Packaging & Display design & implementation (coordinating with printers and clients to ensure brand guidelines were met)
- Created pitch decks for clients & investors directly involved with helping to secure series
 A fundraising